

Han, Jin Chong

Contact

Address

Jie Fang Dong Lu 88hao -tie Cheng Hua Yuan 3hao Lou 2men

Whatsapp

+86 18243300926

Email

jinchong.web@gmail.com

Skype

live:.cid.9eda2a926d35cefa

Telegram

jinchong0115

Discord

jinchong#7371

Skills

- Development Languages(Python, PHP)
- Database and cache(MySQL, MongoDB, Oracle, SQLServer)
- Server (Apache, Nginx, IIS servers)
 - API (REST & SOAP)
 - · Algorithms and data structures

Web Developer

My name is Han, Jin Chong and I have experience for 7+ years in the backend development.

My skills:

Development Languages(Python, PHP)

Database and cache(MySQL, MongoDB, Oracle, SQLServer) Server (Apache, Nginx, IIS servers)

API (REST & SOAP) Development

Algorithms and data structures

My experience and responsibility are:

Development Specialist with 7 years of industry experience and knowledge of onboarding and training employees, effectively planning strategies to meet staff development requirements. Experienced in using learning management systems. Drives training and development across all levels of the company.

Self-motivated Web Developer with a high level of experience working on multiple projects. Passionate and hardworking with a penchant for meeting deadlines. Interested in role with the company promoting best practices and offering diverse customer projects.

Logical and results-driven Web Developer dedicated to building and optimizing user-focused websites for customers with various business objectives. Judicious and creative when crafting effective websites, apps, and platforms to propel competitive advantage and revenue growth. Technically proficient and analytical problem solver with a calm and focused demeanor.

Work Experience

04/2013 - 07/2018

King Star, Jilin, Jilin, China

Software Programmer

- Established network specifications and analyzed workflow, access, information and security requirements
- Implemented, developed and tested installation and update of file servers, print servers and application servers in all departments
- Standardized job tasks and trained junior team members on industry best practices and standards

07/2018 - 12/2019

Self-employed

Full-Stack Developer

I have worked as a freelancer on the Internet.

My experience in: Front-end development with React, Vue,

Back-end development with Django, Laravel

Education

04/2013 - 04/2019

Jilin University

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

Chinese — Native

English — Fluent